<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogger Bust</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blogger Bust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-CA</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2018, all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Licensed Nauci Base Entry With Apache Version 2</title>
      <link>/post/licensed-nauci-base-entry-with-apache-version-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/licensed-nauci-base-entry-with-apache-version-2/</guid>
      <description>Today I released the nauci base init source under Apache version 2.0.
Broken Links I noticed that all of my cross post anchor links are broken. They no longer link to anchors within the post, but instead link to the post itself. I will resolve this issue over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encapsulate Angular WebExtension Dependencies In a Docker Image</title>
      <link>/post/encapsulate-angular-webextension-dependencies-in-a-docker-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/encapsulate-angular-webextension-dependencies-in-a-docker-image/</guid>
      <description>A quick recap The purpose of this article is to provide a concrete example detailing precisely how to encapsulate the dependencies of an Angular WebExtension inside of a docker container whilst keeping the source code and optional tooling on the host system, thereby separating the dependencies from the implementation. In order for the two systems to work in tandem, files that are written to from within the container must remain writable outside of the container and vice versa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Separate Dependencies From Implementation Using POSIX ACL Extended Attributes &amp; Docker</title>
      <link>/post/separate-dependencies-from-implementation-using-nauci-base-entry-docker-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 06:07:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/separate-dependencies-from-implementation-using-nauci-base-entry-docker-image/</guid>
      <description>The motivation I am going to develop a responsive web-extension using angular. The web-extension is for a project that I am starting called nauci. I will talk about nauci more in future posts. In this post I intend to introduce the nauci base entry docker image and how I am using it to encapsulate the nauci project dependencies in a docker sub image, but not the source code. The plan is to bind my local nauci source directory to a docker container built with the nauci dependencies image, thereby separating dependency and tooling concerns from project implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literate Programming</title>
      <link>/post/literate-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 12:43:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/literate-programming/</guid>
      <description>A quick note about my use of Literate Programming My blog is generated using a static site generator called Hugo. Hugo naively supports both Markdown and Org-Mode format, so naturally I have chosen to compose my blog posts in emacs Org-Mode. Org-mode is similar to Markdown in the sense that it uses a simple plain text markup syntax for formatting documents. However, Org-Mode has far more features than Markdown and has fantastic literate programming support via Org-Babel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me My name is Trevor Wilson. I am a software developer and independent contractor residing in Edmonton Alberta, Canada. I have been developing software professionally since 2001 and graduated from the University of Alberta in 2005 with a major mathematics and minor in computing science. One thing that I love about being an independent contractor, is that over the years I have worked for lots of different companies which has allowed me to contribute to a large variety of exciting projects written in many different languages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>