<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Emacs on Blogger Bust</title>
    <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/tags/emacs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Emacs on Blogger Bust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-CA</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2018, all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 12:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bloggerbust.ca/tags/emacs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Appendix</title>
      <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/page/appendix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 12:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloggerbust.ca/page/appendix/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Key-binding notation  Examples  Serial Communication  Comm Parameters Line Speed Additional Reading    
This is where I am going to keep supplemental material that might be useful to reference from multiple pages.
Key-binding notation I follow the emacs key-binding nation when representing keybindings in text. You might be use to seeing CTRL-A to represent holding down the control key followed by the letter a, but in my writings you will see C-a to represent the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Experience Connecting to the PinePhone via Serial Console</title>
      <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/my-first-experience-connecting-to-the-phinephone-via-serial-console/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 05:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/my-first-experience-connecting-to-the-phinephone-via-serial-console/</guid>
      <description>My PinePhone Arrived My PinePhone (BraveHeart edition) arrived a few weeks ago, but I have not had time play with it. Over the weekend I had an epic snowball fight with my wife and children while we were on a nature walk. My Nexus 6p had been neglectfully left in my back pocket and during the escapade it succumbed to fatal injuries. It is time to breath life into my new PinePhone, but first I wanted to have a look around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literate Programming</title>
      <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/literate-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 12:43:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/literate-programming/</guid>
      <description>A quick note about my use of Literate Programming My blog is generated using a static site generator called Hugo. Hugo naively supports both Markdown and Org-Mode format, so naturally I have chosen to compose my blog posts in emacs Org-Mode. Org-mode is similar to Markdown in the sense that it uses a simple plain text markup syntax for formatting documents. However, Org-Mode has far more features than Markdown and has fantastic literate programming support via Org-Babel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>