<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pinephone on Blogger Bust</title>
    <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/tags/pinephone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pinephone on Blogger Bust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-CA</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2018, all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 09:04:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bloggerbust.ca/tags/pinephone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>postmarketOS pmaports Mount Issue</title>
      <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/postmarketos-pmaports-mount-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 09:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/postmarketos-pmaports-mount-issue/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  What is the issue? How to tell if your system is impacted What is the impact? What to do about it? After thoughts   
What is the issue? There are a number of known issues (#258, #661, #664) related to the mounting of the root and boot partitions by fstab when they should be mounted from the initramfs. There is a merge request (https://gitlab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install And Configure PostmarketOS With Plasma Mobile On The PinePhone</title>
      <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/install_and_configure_postmarketos_with_plasma_mobile_on_the_pinephone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 08:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/install_and_configure_postmarketos_with_plasma_mobile_on_the_pinephone/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Introduction What not to post online Setting up the build environment  Ensure ~/.local/bin exists Install or clone pmbootstrap Clone pmaports  Initialize the pmbootstrap configuration for the pinephone Identify the block special file name Deploy to the SD card A bit about LUKS  Determine if a partition is LUKS encrypted Determine the format of a LUKS encrypted partition A quick look at a LUKS header Test mounting our LUKS Encrypted Partition  NCurses Over Serial Boot into postmarketOS Resize the screen Set the timezone, date &amp;amp; time What&amp;rsquo;s in the default runlevel?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Experience Connecting to the PinePhone via Serial Console</title>
      <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/my-first-experience-connecting-to-the-phinephone-via-serial-console/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 05:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/my-first-experience-connecting-to-the-phinephone-via-serial-console/</guid>
      <description>My PinePhone Arrived My PinePhone (BraveHeart edition) arrived a few weeks ago, but I have not had time play with it. Over the weekend I had an epic snowball fight with my wife and children while we were on a nature walk. My Nexus 6p had been neglectfully left in my back pocket and during the escapade it succumbed to fatal injuries. It is time to breath life into my new PinePhone, but first I wanted to have a look around.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>