<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tty on Blogger Bust</title>
    <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/tags/tty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tty on Blogger Bust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-CA</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2018, all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 12:10:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bloggerbust.ca/tags/tty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Let SOcket CAT Be Thy Glue Over Serial</title>
      <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/let-socket-cat-be-thy-glue-over-serial/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 12:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/let-socket-cat-be-thy-glue-over-serial/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I previously wrote how to configure minicom to connect to a device over serial UART. In that post I mentioned that minicom might not be the best tool for the job. Consider that minicom is adding a lot of unnecessary complexity. If you think about it, we are taking a command line utility intended for communicating with modems, stripping all that functionality away so that we are left with nothing more than a terminal emulator that knows how to connect to a foreign TTY.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Configure Minicom To Connect Over USB Serial UART</title>
      <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/how-to-configure-minicom-to-connect-over-usb-serial-uart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/how-to-configure-minicom-to-connect-over-usb-serial-uart/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I recently wrote about my first experience connecting to the pinephone via serial console. This post documents how to configure Minicom for establishing an interactive terminal session with a device connected to your computer via a serial port. The configuration will be saved to file so that it can be reused to connect to the same device again in the future, which is convenient. My version of minicom at the time of writing is minicom version 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Experience Connecting to the PinePhone via Serial Console</title>
      <link>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/my-first-experience-connecting-to-the-phinephone-via-serial-console/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 05:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloggerbust.ca/post/my-first-experience-connecting-to-the-phinephone-via-serial-console/</guid>
      <description>My PinePhone Arrived My PinePhone (BraveHeart edition) arrived a few weeks ago, but I have not had time play with it. Over the weekend I had an epic snowball fight with my wife and children while we were on a nature walk. My Nexus 6p had been neglectfully left in my back pocket and during the escapade it succumbed to fatal injuries. It is time to breath life into my new PinePhone, but first I wanted to have a look around.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>